Yeesha: The Journeys are complete. Now take the final pillar. Take it, but hear all I've said.
Yeesha: It's the whispers and murmurs that reveal the simple truths.
Yeesha: You hold the precious soul of a Bahro in your Age, in your hand.  Such things are not meant to be held.
Yeesha: Do what I do. I have learned things, seen things, written things they never thought possible.
Yeesha: I have seen the real treasures that are protected by the petty fences of their rules.
Yeesha: I have found the precious gold buried deep beneath the weighty mountains of their laws.
Yeesha: This is my journey too. I am returning what has been given.
Yeesha: These years I've spent, this path I've traveled, this gift I've been given. This purpose weighs on me, my burden, the legacy of my father, Atrus.
Yeesha: For we are shaping D'ni. We will mold what comes after.
Yeesha: We cannot keep the power and the pride from ruining this new D'ni, but we can prepare those who will read between the lines.
Yeesha: The Least are returning. The stream in the Cleft is returning. Life is returning. The Fissure is returning.
Yeesha: The circle will be completed when you give back what you have taken.
Yeesha: You must return.