Yeesha: Shorah. Peace to you, mover of the Least.
Yeesha: Seven more Journeys have moved you closer.
Yeesha: I was seduced while in D'ni.
Yeesha: My humble darkness lasted only a short time before I began to bask in what I could do, what I could write.
Yeesha: My gift, my path. The knowledge of my father and the dreams of my mother pierced a hole in the darkness. In the weakness.
Yeesha: I was aware of my power and I was proud.
Yeesha: Whole worlds at my fingertips.
Yeesha: It was the same with the D'ni, the same cycle. Light opens the darkness. It takes, it uses, and it keeps.
Yeesha: The D'ni found power in these books, these books you use to travel. They were a gift from the Maker.
Yeesha: These Ages you travel to were their Ages. Remarkable places giving life, and taking life.
Yeesha: This shadow came over them, this shadow of light, for it was in their enlightenment that they considered themselves better; better than the Least.
Yeesha: And we were sad for them.
Yeesha: Can you feel the D'ni there? You've touched the remnants, the remains of their pride and power.