Yeesha: Shorah. Rekooahn trekleft preniv legloen b'rem.
Yeesha: Oh yes, not in D'ni. They won't understand.
Yeesha: Once again the stream in the Cleft has begun to flow.
Yeesha: It was dry for so long.
Yeesha: The water is flowing in from the desert.
Yeesha: The storm is coming.
Yeesha: Have you heard of the city? The deep city, the ancient Uru?
Yeesha: Where there was power to write worlds.
Yeesha: For thousands of years, the city lived... lived beneath the surface. Keeper of the secret, keeper of the power, keeper of the Ages.
Yeesha: Always keeping.
Yeesha: The city grew proud. And then it died.
Yeesha: The water flows where it wills.
Yeesha: It seeks its own path uncontrolled except that it flows downward, always downward.
Yeesha: D'ni, the city of Ages, of other worlds, died. But now it breathes again, it awaits.
Yeesha: Some will seek that destination, but you should seek the Journey.
Yeesha: It's as a fine tapestry, complex beyond comprehension, but now torn.
Yeesha: We will show you remnants; pieces of the tapestry. Pieces of the Journey.
Yeesha: Find these remnants, these Journeys. Seven. Seven in each Age. Seven here in the desert.
Yeesha: Consider it a quest. No, a request.
Yeesha: Worship.
Yeesha: The water flows downward, and there it pools and collects, and finally once again... it reaches the roots.
Yeesha: And the tree begins to grow again.
Yeesha: I am Yeesha. My parents brought me to this place.
Yeesha: We will bring you.