Yeesha: An ending has been written?
Yeesha: You've done all that has been asked. You've traveled the full circle. You have returned to the Cleft through the Fissure.
Yeesha: You swam among the stars and saw the remnants of previous Journeys.
Yeesha: You have returned, and the pillars were returned. And now one more of the Bahro, the Least, has been returned to D'ni.
Yeesha: You don't need to understand what that means, only that the hand of the Maker has set it in motion.
Yeesha: Now the circle is complete and the Tree has begun to grow again. The path is now open, and so the symbol of the Journey must change.
Yeesha: Now the beginning is tied to the end. Now you can go where you wish.
Yeesha: The restoration of D'ni awaits.
Yeesha: The deep city breathes. Uru again.
Yeesha: And I will be concerned with other things.
Yeesha: The Least are becoming greater. They will now also affect the restoration, perhaps not the way others had planned.
Yeesha: You've learned about the pride of D'ni. The great writers of worlds were infected with pride that became a cancer.
Yeesha: It grew quietly beneath the surface, but it grew until D'ni could live no more.
Yeesha: But those things have been told. You understand it well, I think.
Yeesha: Let us end this cycle with rewards, before we start the next cycle.
Yeesha: Relto. The high place. Your Age now. It was the first Age I wrote, a gift for my parents, and now much more.
Yeesha: It reminds me of another home, another place. I even placed the library in the place it belongs.
Yeesha: But Relto will change. It will be your soul, showing what you are.
Yeesha: Only I could write Relto. It's beyond what the D'ni could accomplish. Keep it.
Yeesha: And I've given you clothing that represents your Journey. Wear this to show others what side you've taken, when sides are taken.
Yeesha: When you wear it, you will tell all that you side with us. With Yeesha, with the Bahro. It will not always be easy.
Yeesha: And another gift is here. A link to the Cleft, here in Tomahna.
Yeesha: You haven't been able to return here, but now you can.
Yeesha: This Book will take a special place on your shelf. This place is not meant to be shared.
Yeesha: Return here alone when you wish to remember the cycle of things.